# **Erick Latshaw**

erickjlatshaw@gmail.com | Linkedin | Github | Portfolio

Junior Game Programmer

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a passionate programmer and game developer with abilities in both 2D and 3D game creation. I have experience working in game jams as well as longer team projects. I am incredibly comfortable with version control and I pride myself in my clean code and game architecture with an emphasis on making designer-friendly, decoupled systems.

## **SKILLS**

Git Version Control, Unity, Unreal Engine, C#, C++

#### **PROJECT EXPERIENCE**

SEPTEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

Heavenly Sin, Unity, 13-person Team - 3D Dialogue-driven murder mystery/platforming game set in the 1920s

- Lead Programmer and manager of github throughout the entire project with no major loss of work
- Made and enforced a style guide as well as a github guide for team members
- Developed player controls, UI functionality, audio manager, settings manager, and save and load system
- Used scriptable objects as data containers, items, and events

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

**Derpy Derby**, Unity, 2-person Team - Online multiplayer party game where players control low-poly cars and smash into each other until there's a winner.

- Managed github
- Developed car controller, audio manager, car stats, networking, settings manager, server list

OCTOBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

**Spooker**, Unity, 2-person GameJam - Halloween themed game where you play as a ghost and scare candy from NPCs without being seen.

- Managed github
- Developed player controls, procedurally generated play field, AI movement for the NPCS
- win/loss conditions, line-of-sight cones, and functionality to scare candy out of NPCs depending on proximity to them.

## **EDUCATION**

Expected May 2022

Marist College, Poughkeepsie, NY

BS, Games & Emerging Media - Technical Concentration